<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubuntu Korea Community Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ubuntu Korea Community Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 10:50:36 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FOSSASIA Summit 2023 retrospection</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2023/04/23/fossasia-2023-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 10:50:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2023/04/23/fossasia-2023-recap/</guid>
      <description>FOSSASIA Summit has been held online in past few years due to COVID-19, but this year, the event has been held in-person finally. I participated in the online event last year as an organizer and worked in the marketing team and the video team. But, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t participate in this year&amp;rsquo;s FOSSASIA event as an organizer. Because when the FOSSASIA team was built this year, I was so busy a few weeks ahead the UbuCon Asia 2022 event in Korea and I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know the team was being created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us UbuCon Asia in-person in Seoul this November!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/11/11/ubucon-asia-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/11/11/ubucon-asia-2022/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia is an event by Ubuntu Communities in Asia that brings together hundreds of Ubuntu users, developers, contributors, enthusiasts and many other interested people.
It is a place to share experiences and discussion around Ubuntu, as well as being a festival that Ubuntu and other open source communities can enjoy.
Why join in-person? There will be exciting Talks and Workshops with a wide range of topics! From Cloud and Infrastructure, Desktop, Community, IoT to WSL topics and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 22.04 LTS Jammy Jellyfish Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/04/22/jamme-jellyfish-release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 02:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/04/22/jamme-jellyfish-release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Jammy Jellyfish Release Notes Introduction These release notes for Ubuntu 22.04 LTS (Jammy Jellyfish) provide an overview of the release and document the known issues with Ubuntu and its flavours.
Support lifespan Maintenance updates will be provided for 5 years until April 2027 for Ubuntu Desktop, Ubuntu Server, Ubuntu Cloud, and Ubuntu Core. All the remaining flavours will be supported for 3 years. Additional security support is available with ESM (Extended Security Maintenance).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to this blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/contribute/</guid>
      <description>If you are organizer or person who participates Ubuntu Korea Community, You can contribute your own posting to this blog.
For organizers First, You must be a member of ubuntu-kr organization on GitHub. You will also need read and write acccess to ubuntu-kr/blog.ubuntu-kr.org repository. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have yet, Ask may other organizers for that.
After gaining all access you need, Clone ubuntu-kr/blog.ubuntu-kr.org repository to your machine, And get started with writting post with steps that can be found on this README.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
