<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ubuntu Korea Community Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ubuntu Korea Community Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Join us UbuCon Asia in-person in Seoul this November!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/11/11/ubucon-asia-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/11/11/ubucon-asia-2022/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia is an event by Ubuntu Communities in Asia that brings together hundreds of Ubuntu users, developers, contributors, enthusiasts and many other interested people.
It is a place to share experiences and discussion around Ubuntu, as well as being a festival that Ubuntu and other open source communities can enjoy.
Why join in-person? There will be exciting Talks and Workshops with a wide range of topics! From Cloud and Infrastructure, Desktop, Community, IoT to WSL topics and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 22.04 LTS Jammy Jellyfish Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/04/22/jamme-jellyfish-release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 02:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/04/22/jamme-jellyfish-release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Jammy Jellyfish Release Notes Introduction These release notes for Ubuntu 22.04 LTS (Jammy Jellyfish) provide an overview of the release and document the known issues with Ubuntu and its flavours.
Support lifespan Maintenance updates will be provided for 5 years until April 2027 for Ubuntu Desktop, Ubuntu Server, Ubuntu Cloud, and Ubuntu Core. All the remaining flavours will be supported for 3 years. Additional security support is available with ESM (Extended Security Maintenance).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
