<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ubucon on Ubuntu Korea Community Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/tags/ubucon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ubucon on Ubuntu Korea Community Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/tags/ubucon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LibreOffice Conf X UbuCon Asia 2023 in Indonesia recap</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2023/11/01/louca23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2023/11/01/louca23/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia, which started as an online event in 2021, is now in its third year. This year&amp;rsquo;s event was held in Surakarta, Indonesia, and was a joint event with LibreOffice Conf Asia, making it a much bigger event than in previous years. I participated in the organizing committee for this year&amp;rsquo;s event as well as last year&amp;rsquo;s, but last year&amp;rsquo;s event was held in Seoul, so I was mainly part of the local team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us UbuCon Asia in-person in Seoul this November!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/11/11/ubucon-asia-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ubuntu-kr.org/en/2022/11/11/ubucon-asia-2022/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia is an event by Ubuntu Communities in Asia that brings together hundreds of Ubuntu users, developers, contributors, enthusiasts and many other interested people.
It is a place to share experiences and discussion around Ubuntu, as well as being a festival that Ubuntu and other open source communities can enjoy.
Why join in-person? There will be exciting Talks and Workshops with a wide range of topics! From Cloud and Infrastructure, Desktop, Community, IoT to WSL topics and more!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
